<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DailyNews</string>
    <string name="aboutInfo">
        \n\n<b><u>History</u></b>\n
 \n\tB. K. Birla Institute of Engineering and Technology is one of the premier industry-oriented and application-driven institutes in India.Shree Krishnarpan Charity Trust, under Chairmanship of renowned industrialist Mr Basant Kumar Birla, set up BKBIET, in 2007.

\n\n\tThe Institution has been true to its commitment in providing quality education in Engineering and Technology. Our strong alliances with leading international universities, industries and professional bodies have increased access to latest education, opportunities for engagement and exchange, collaborative research and innovation for our students and faculties. We believe the best way to help BKBIETians meet challenges is to provide a supportive and enriching environment.

        \n\n<b><u>Vision</u></b>\n
\n\tExcel as an outstanding application-oriented and innovation-driven engineering institute. Inspire future Engineers to apply technology for solving real world challenges.

        \n\n<b><u>Mission</u></b>\n
\n\tCreate a platform for igniting ingenuity and path-breaking engineering applications for the India of future.

        \n\n<b><u>Recognition and Affiliation</u></b>\n
\n\tB. K. Birla Institute of Engineering and Technology, Pilani is approved by AICTE and affiliated to the Rajasthan Technical University (RTU) 2007-2017 and Bikaner Technical University (BTU) 2018 onwards.

        \n\n<b><u>Director’s Message</u></b>\n
\n\tI heartily welcome students, industry professionals and research institutions to BKBIET.

\n\n\tIt gives great pride to mention that BKBIET has achieved an enviable national and international reputation for research, and teaching excellence in a short span of 11 years.

\n\n\tInstitute takes pride in introducing B. Tech Artificial Intelligence Engineering from coming session 2020-21. It aims to groom incoming students into academically strong yet well-rounded personality based professionals who could adapt themselves to the challenges posed by the ever-changing world and working environments.

\n\n\tOur strength is highly qualified and dedicated faculty members and staff deeply engaged in research work and scientific collaboration in national and international projects. Our students are very innovative and always eager to learn new concepts; they have demonstrated their capabilities and brilliance in many fields including securing internship in highly reputed international organizations.

\n\n\tIn line with our vision and strategy for future, BKBIET will continue to drive for improvement. While reputation is important, we care as much about your individual experience as we do about our position on global scale.

\n\n\tExplore world through our application-driven and industry-oriented programmes.

\n\n\t\t\t\t– Dr Prasanna Kumar S M

    </string>
</resources>